Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
What's going on?
We are at a park.
It's a nice day.
It's a nice day, but it's freezing.
It's freezing.
Today,
you usually travel by car, right?
Yes.
But,
you might have to travel by bicycle.
That's going to be tough.
I don't want to.
I can't.
You can't carry a suitcase in a basket.
I thought you might have to travel by
bicycle.
Yes.
I heard that
you can't ride a bicycle.
Who?
Who can't ride a bicycle?
I can't believe it.
Who is it?
It's me.
I heard that
you can't ride a bicycle.
when you have to ride a bicycle,
someone has to ride a bicycle
for you.
That's going to be tough.
I'm going to be a burden.
That's what I heard.
So,
we are going to teach you how to ride a
bicycle.
So,
we are going to teach you
how to ride a bicycle.
I'm going to teach you seriously.
We are going to teach you
how to ride a bicycle.
Leave it to me.
I'm going to teach you.
Of course.
I'm worried because I saw you playing
basketball.
Don't worry.
It doesn't matter whether you have good
or bad motor skills.
I'm also known as
the bicycle queen.
I'm famous in the street.
So,
I'm going to teach you
how to ride a bicycle.
I'm going to teach you how to ride a
bicycle.
Thank you.
I hope you can ride a bicycle
and go home.
I see.
I'm looking forward to your feedback.
Leave it to me.
Let's get started.
Let's go.
Let's ride a bicycle.
I prepared a bicycle.
I brought it from the sky.
Thank you.
I don't know what you are riding.
I've never seen you riding a bicycle.
I think I can ride a bicycle.
Let's see how good you are.
Leave it to me.
I'm scared.
I can't ride a bicycle.
You are not in a good posture.
I'm not in a good posture.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Did you ride a bicycle?
Well...
Yes.
I can't ride a bicycle alone.
So, I'll ask you
to teach me how to ride a bicycle.
I see.
I want to ride a bicycle.
Wow
Let's start the bicycle lesson!
Let's do it!
Are you ready?
Yes!
This is a matter of spirit.
I'll imitate you.
Yes!
Wow!
OK. Checking is over.
Yes!
Well, then,
First, I'll imitate your fear.
I see.
You don't want to fall down.
In order to pay the fee,
please imitate me.
Again?
Yes!
Wow!
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
Did you pay the fee?
Yes!
Next, I'll imitate your posture.
I see.
Karen, you were standing like this.
Yes!
I'll imitate your posture.
Are you ready?
Do it at the same time.
Ready?
Peeing!
Do it more.
Ready?
Peeing!
Do it more.
Ready?
Peeing!
OK!
I'm watching you.
Next, we have to get along with
bicycles.
We have to get along with them.
Yes, we do.
In order to get along with bicycles,
let's introduce ourselves.
I see.
How should we introduce ourselves?
First, your profile.
Name, age, birthplace, age, birthplace,
and where you were born.
And your recommendation in Tohoku.
I see.
And what kind of person you want to be
in the future.
And what kind of relationship you want
to have with bicycles.
I see.
You have a lot of things to say.
And your worries.
I see.
Let's start with your profile.
Yes.
Thank you for watching this video.
I'm 18 years old, from Miyagi
prefecture.
The sparrows of Tohoku are the eggs of
the duckweed.
I want to be in a relationship where
people support each other, regardless of
their origin.
I think that bicycles are a very easy
and familiar existence among the means
of transportation.
I want to be loved by everyone as an
idol.
What are your recent worries?
I'm worried about how to live as a
leader.
I want you to tell me.
It's heavy.
I think I can accept bicycles because
I've revealed myself.
I think you can understand the feeling
of the tire.
I want to massage the tire.
Do you want to do it?
The tire may be a little hard.
I'm going.
It's hard.
It's not hard.
The air is in the tire.
It's hard.
It's very hard.
It's good.
It's getting loose.
I think I've connected with the
bicycle.
I think so, too.
I can know my partner and reveal
myself.
I like your face color.
Shall we ride on the bicycle?
Yes.
Let's ride on the bicycle.
You should put your feet on the pedal.
Yes.
Look at the back of the bicycle.
Look at the front of the bicycle.
I think I'm looking at the front of the
bicycle too much.
You should put your feet on the pedal.
You should put your feet on the pedal
as much as you can.
Yes.
Let's go.
Ready, go!
Stop.
The direction of the bicycle changes.
I see.
Let's go again.
Yes.
Slowly.
Wow.
It's right. Yes.
Oh, my body is twisted.
Like this?
Let's try it again.
Can you show me how to ride it? Sure.
Let me go.
Let's go.
Go! Wow.
I'm watching you.
I see.
I think I can do it.
I feel like I'm elegant.
I see.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The pedal is always bent.
I see.
It stops.
Yes, it stops.
Let's go as you see.
Ready, go!
Please subscribe to this channel!
I can do it!
I have entered the camera.
Are you OK?
I have never seen this kind of movement
in animation.
It was amazing.
Look forward!
OK!
Move your hands along the path.
Look far!
OK!
It is the same as Mario Kart.
I see.
It is slanted.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Oh!
It's OK!
Look at the distance!
OK!
Oh!
Mi-kun, try to release it!
You can do it!
You can control it by yourself!
Let's go to the edge!
Oh!
I'm not pushing the button.
Really?
Let's push it harder.
OK.
It's more stable.
Let go of Miya.
Stop.
You're great.
Great.
I'm not pushing the button.
Wow!
If you go by yourself from the
beginning, you can't do it.
Let me go.
Like this.
OK.
I'll be like this.
So, I'll go like this, as if I'm
controlling the bicycle.
I'll do what you said.
I'll ride it.
Let's go to the middle.
Thank you.
I'll go.
Yes!
Awesome!
Watch out!
Yes!
You're doing great!
Stop!
Awesome!
You did it!
I did it!
You're great, Kohko!
You have potential.
Thank you for teaching me.
I didn't expect you to do it so
quickly.
I was surprised.
It's a story of a sudden success.
It's a touching story.
I was surprised.
It's the most valuable video I've ever
seen.
It's amazing!
Awesome!
It's a touching BGM.
Thank you.
I did it!
I'm glad.
I can ride a bicycle even if I have to
direct it.
I can ride it.
Can you ride a bicycle in Shinjuku?
No.
I can't.
Then, I'll ride a bicycle with you.
I think you could ride a bicycle
because you weren't afraid.
You can't ride a bicycle if you're
afraid.
I felt good.
The wind was blowing.
It's fun.
Next time, we'll have a story of a
sudden success.
Finally, nine of us will ride a
bicycle.
I want to ride a bicycle.
We'll sing a song while riding a
bicycle.
Singing?
I'm a little dizzy.
You made us cry.
Really?
There are other stories.
I'm afraid I'll get a pain.
I'm embarrassed.
It was a story of a sudden success.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you can't ride a bicycle, please
watch this video and learn how to ride a
bicycle.
If you have any trouble, please look up
how to ride a bicycle in Tohoku.
If you're in trouble, please look it
up.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Please try to ride a bicycle.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Wow!
Go!
Bye bye!